<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PidevMobile</string>
    <string name="homepage">YOUR LEADING COMPETITIVE GAMING PLATFORM</string>
    <string name="choose_your_game">CHOOSE YOUR GAME</string>
    <string name="join">JOIN COMMUNITY.</string>
    <string name="play">Play with over 22 million gamers in leagues,            tournaments and ladders</string>
    <string name="matchmaking">MATCHMAKING Get matched with like-minded gamers and compete for prizes.</string>
    <string name="ac">ANTI-CHEAT WINIT Anti-Cheat has banned over 120,000 cheaters!</string>
    <string name="tournament">TOURNAMENTS Compete for real prizes with friends and other players</string>
    <string name="skillprog">SKILL PROGRESSION Track your stats as you climb the ranks</string>
    <string name="getstarted">Get Started</string>
    <string name="bettergamestitle">PLAY BETTER GAMES</string>
    <string name="bettergamescontent">Find others to play with in seconds! You’ll get matched with equally ranked and like-minded gamers to improve your skill and learn from the best.</string>
    <string name="csgo">Global Offensive, like prior games in the Counter-Strike series, is an objective-based, multiplayer first-person shooter. Two opposing teams, the Terrorists and the Counter-Terrorists, compete in game modes to repeatedly complete objectives, such as securing a location to plant or defuse a bomb and rescuing or capturing hostages. At the end of each short round, players are rewarded based on individual and team performance with in-game currency to spend on other weapons or utility in subsequent rounds. Winning rounds generally rewards more money than losing does, and completing map-based objectives, including killing enemies, gives additional cash bonuses.An in-progress match on Dust II, in which the player is using an AK-47. Global Offensive has nine official game modes: Competitive, Casual, Deathmatch, Arms Race, Demolition, Wingman, Flying Scoutsman, Retakes and Danger Zone. Competitive mode, the primary gameplay experience, pits two teams of five players against each other in a best-of-30 match. When playing Competitive, players have a skill rank based on an Elo rating system and are paired with and against other players around the same ranking. The Casual and Deathmatch modes are less serious than Competitive mode and do not register friendly fire. Both are primarily used as a practice tool. Arms Race and Demolition, both based on mods for previous iterations in the series, were added alongside eight new maps for the modes. Arms Race is the Global Offensive variant of the "Gun Game" mode in other games in the series. Demolition is another bomb defusal game mode, with gun upgrades only given to players who killed an enemy in the previous round. Wingman is a two-on-two bomb defusal game mode taking place over sixteen rounds. Similar to Competitive, players are paired based on a dynamic skill ranking. The Flying Scoutsman mode equips players with only a SSG 08 (known in-game as the "Scout") and a knife in a low-gravity map. Retakes is a gamemode where three Terrorists will defend an already planted C4 against 4 Counter-Terrorists. Players will also be able to choose a loadout card at the beginning of each round to retake (or defend) the bomb site. Danger Zone is a battle-royale mode in which up to 18 players search for weapons, equipment, and money in an effort to be the last person or team remaining. Valve also included an offline practice mode designed to help new players learn how to use guns and grenades, called the Weapons Course. Apart from the Weapons Course, all other game modes can be played online or offline with bots. There are five categories of purchasable weaponry: rifles, submachine guns, "heavy" weaponry (light machine guns and shotguns), pistols, and grenades. Each gun in Global Offensive has a unique recoil pattern that can be controlled, a gameplay feature the series has long been associated with. Global Offensive also introduced weapons and equipment not seen in previous installments, including tasers and an incendiary grenade. In-game matchmaking is supported for all online game modes and is managed through the Steam platform. The game servers run Valve Anti-Cheat to prevent cheating. One form of matchmaking in Global Offensive to prevent cheating, Prime Matchmaking, hosts matches that can only be played with other users with the "Prime" status. This feature also results in more equal matches as there are fewer "smurfs" in these matches. The PC version of Global Offensive also supports private dedicated servers that players may connect to through the community server menu in-game. These servers may be heavily modified and can drastically differ from the base game modes. There have been many community made mods for the game, one of the popular ones being "kz", a mod that makes players complete obstacle courses requiring advanced strafing and jumping techniques.</string>
    <string name="valorant">Valorant is a team-based first-person hero shooter set in the near future. Players play as one of a set of agents, characters designed based on several countries and cultures around the world. In the main game mode, players are assigned to either the attacking or defending team with each team having five players on it. Agents have unique abilities, each requiring charges, as well as a unique ultimate ability that requires charging through kills, deaths, orbs, or spike actions. Every player starts each round with a "classic" pistol and one or more "signature ability" charges. Other weapons and ability charges can be purchased using an in-game economic system that awards money based on the outcome of the previous round, any kills the player is responsible for, and any actions taken with the spike. The game has an assortment of weapons including secondary guns like sidearms and primary guns like submachine guns, shotguns, machine guns, assault rifles and sniper rifles. There are automatic and semi-automatic weapons that each have a unique shooting pattern that has to be controlled by the player to be able to shoot accurately. Different agents allow players to find more ways to plant the Spike and style on enemies with scrappers, strategists, and hunters of every description. It currently offers 16 agents to choose from. They are Brimstone, Viper, Omen, Cypher, Sova, Sage, Phoenix, Jett, Raze, Breach, Reyna, Killjoy, Skye, Yoru, Astra, and KAY/O.</string>
    <string name="csgopatchnotes">Release Notes for 10/21/2021 [STOCKHOLM 2021 CS:GO MAJOR CHAMPIONSHIP] – The “Stockholm 2021 Viewer Pass” and the “Stockholm 2021 Viewer Pass + 3 Souvenir Tokens” are now available for purchase. 50% of the proceeds go to the teams and organizations taking part in the PGL Stockholm 2021 CS:GO Major Championship. – With a Viewer Pass, you’ll get: — An upgradable Stockholm 2021 Event Coin. — Access to the Stockholm Pick’Em Challenge. — Unlimited team graffiti for the duration of the event. — Steam.tv team flair. — Access to Stockholm 2021 Souvenir Packages. – Team stickers and patches are available for purchase. [MISC] – Enabled grenade donation purchases from the buy wheel. – Fixed a bug where spectators sometimes wouldn’t correctly see donated weapons. – Fixed a bug where disconnected and reconnected players could exceed grenade purchase limits. [AI – BEHAVIOR TREES] – Added the following nodes: decorator_game_event, action_drop_active_weapon, action_inspect_current_weapon, action_standup, action_custom_buy. – Added variables: BombIsBeingDefused, AccountBalance, IsBlind, BlindnessPercentage. – Fixed a bug where node “condition_owns_item” wouldn’t work with “item_defuser” / “item_cutters”. – Fixed a bug where bots would incorrectly include themselves when sensing other players. – Added support for “team_filter” when sensing grenades. – Node “action_wait” now supports “@convar” references. Release Notes for 10/15/2021 [ MISC ] – Fixed a bug where water footstep sounds would emit from spectating players’ death locations. – Bots will be able to open more Danger Zone doors. – Stability improvements. [ MAPS ] Ancient – Fixed pixel gap through scaffolding near B Basalt – Fixed many clipping issues (thanks Luar) – Fixed missing nav mesh in lower A – Updated radar – Made map playable again by changing the license plates – Various visual tweaks</string>
    <string name="valopatchnotes">VALORANT PATCH NOTES 3.09 Along with the new VALORANT Act III Battlepass and Competitive refresh (there’s also that new Agent arriving later), we put the Classic through some honing and rearranged some furniture on Fracture. Read the rest below. WEAPON UPDATES CLASSIC (RIGHT-CLICK) The Classic has been over-performing in close to mid-range encounters when used while jumping or on the move. So we’ve reduced the weapon’s effective accuracy while jumping, running, and walking, with the intent of narrowing it’s ideal use case to only really close ranges. Walking firing error changed .05 >>> .6 (total error is 2.5 when walking, up from 1.95) Running firing error changed .2 >>> 1.3 (total error is 3.2 when running, up from 2.1) Jumping firing error changed from 1.1 >>> 2.1 (total error is 4.0 when jumping, up from 3.0) MAP UPDATES FRACTURE The B Arcade attacker barrier is shifted back towards Attacker Side Bridge, to allow defenders to more easily contest the area Defender barrier at A Rope moved up to the top of ropes to make it easier for Sentinels to prepare. A Hall orb shifted into more neutral space, making it less favorable for attackers New piece of cover in Attacker spawn added to break the long sightline from Hall entrance to B Main, which should relieve some pressure from attackers when defenders fast flank GAME SYSTEMS UPDATES Smoother Ropes/Ziplines Fixed jittery movement that could occur when stopping or changing directions on a zipline or rope. This was most noticeable when repeatedly moving a small amount and stopping. ESPORTS FEATURES Observers using gamepad controllers are no longer locked out of the X/Y axes when speeding up with the right bumper (R1). Free Cam observers rejoice! Observers now have the option to set handedness for teams When this option is toggled, observers will see players that start the match on attacker as right-handed, and players that start the match on defender will be left-handed. GENERAL One path for all traffic into game servers For those of you particular to a preferred server, you may notice a previously preferred location is no longer there. Don’t worry, we simply consolidated what was two paths into the game servers into one—we did not remove any servers. BUGS COMPETITIVE Fixed a bug that was causing the default Act Rank badge to display on Unrated game loading screens AGENTS Cypher can no longer place Spycam on the Breeze door in order to destroy or see through the door when its lowered. Similarly, fixed random spots where Cypher could not place Spycam in the same area. Fixed bug that displayed Jett’s 1P Updraft visuals incorrectly</string>
</resources>